# ILONA SKARGOVSKAYA

FRONTEND DEVELOPER

+972-534-762-486

✓ ilona.skars@gmail.com

Maifa district, Kiryat Yam

in linkedIn/ilona-skargovskaya/

gitHub/IlonaSkargovskaya

## SKILLS

- HTML5 & CSS (SASS)
- Python
- OOP
- SQL (relational)
- Django
- JavaScript
- Node.js
- React
- Figma / Adobe Photoshop
- WordPress CMS
- SEO & Influencer marketing

# **EDUCATION**

#### **FULLSTACK DEVELOPMENT**

Developers Institute, TLV Coding Bootcamp (Israel)

Apr 2023 - Present

#### FRONTEND DEVELOPMENT

The Rolling Scopes School (EPAM)

Mar 2022 - Dec 2022

# BACHELOR OF SOFTWARE DEVELOPMENT

Belarusian State University of Informatics and Radioelectronics

Sep 2012 - May 2016

### **SOFTWARE TECHNICIAN**

Minsk Radioengineering College

Sep 2008 - May 2012

## SUMMARY

I am a qualified and professional frontend developer with 5 years of experience in designing and laying out websites. I also have a background in Python and JavaScript, enabling me to create dynamic and interactive web experiences. My combination of creative and analytical skills allows me to balance aesthetic appeal with functional efficiency. A team player who pays close attention to detail.

## TECHNICAL PROJECTS

App Name - Github | Demo

Brief description of the app's functionality and purpose

- Action verb + what did + result
- · Action verb + what did + result
- Action verb + what did + result

### EXPERIENCE

### **DIGITAL MARKETING SPECIALIST**

Freelance

May 2018 - Present

- Create and organize original, high-quality video-content
- Collaborate with brands and businesses to produce sponsored content, product reviews and promotions
- Do consulting for entrepreneurs on starting and promoting their businesses in social networks

### **FOUNDER**

May 2018 - Dec 2022

Kids.by

- · Developed comprehensive printing solutions for kids event
- Created full range of services from design to finished products, using plotter cutting, embossing and printing equipment

### WEB-DEVELOPER TEAM LEADER

Minsk state concert organization (Belarus)

Sep 2014 - Jan 2020

- Created more than 60 personal, promotional and commercial websites for different state projects with a unique design based on CMS Wordpress and CMS Joomla
- Successfully led and managed a team of seven people
- Utilized Photoshop to design and created promotional products

### WEBSITE LAYOUT DESIGNER

Internet agency "WEBMEDIA"

May 2012 - Aug 2014

- Transformed Photoshop design concepts into responsive and visually appealing web pages
- Implemented strategic SEO promotion initiatives to optimize website performance and increase organic visibility

### **LANGUAGES**

English - Fluent Russian - Native Hebrew - Intermediate